A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Education, Media, Arts and Culture (EMAC) - Education, Knowledge, and Religion Unit (EKR), Office Files of Toby Alice Volkman FA712
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Other Grants and Subjects, 1982-2001; III
  - Peace, Equality and Governance, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Pennsylvania State University – Against All Odds, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Program Officer Memo (POM), 1999 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Reflections and Exit Memoranda, 1997-2001 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Religion – Curriculum Vitae, 1990s (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Religion – Culture and Religion Consultative Subgroup, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Religion – Foundation grant making related to, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Religion – Planning notes and email, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Resignation announcement, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Resume, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Rethinking Area Studies conference, 1995-1997 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Rethinking Area Studies memoranda and drafts, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Revitalizing Area Studies conference, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Rice University, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Rutgers University – African Studies Coordinating Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Rutgers University – Center for the Critical Analysis of Contemporary Culture, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Rutgers University – Latin American Studies – Writers at the Border, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Science, 1990s (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Social Science Research Council – Bangladesh Studies, 1990-1996 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Social Science Research Council – Collective Memories of Repression, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Social Science Research Council – Core grant, 1991-1996 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Social Science Research Council – Core grant, 1997-2000 (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
  - Social Science Research Council - Cultural Agency in the Americas, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Social Science Research Council - International Dissertation Field Research Fellowship, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Social Science Research Council - International Predissertation Fellowship Program – General, 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 6-8)
  - Social Science Research Council - International Predissertation Fellowship Program – Committee meetings, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 9-10)
  - Social Science Research Council - International Predissertation Fellowship Program – Fellows conference, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Social Science Research Council - International Predissertation Fellowship Program – Fellows report, 1991-1996 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Social Science Research Council - International Predissertation Fellowship Program – Recommendations for Grants Action (RGAs), 1993-1997 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Social Science Research Council - New International Program, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Social Science Research Council - Regional Advisory Panels, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Social Science Research Council - Reports on Ford Foundation-funded projects, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Social Science Research Council - Southeast Asian Studies, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Social Science Research Council - Vietnamese Studies Fellowship Program, 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Social Sciences Research and Development Forum, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Southeast Asia Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Stanford University – Institute for International Studies, 1993-1996 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Stephens, Robert F., 1997 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Tufts College – Navajo Oral History and Photography, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - United Negro College Fund – International Education Project, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - United States-Indonesia Society, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - United States Information Agency, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - University of California, Berkeley – Culture and Environment, 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - University of California, Berkeley – Vietnam Studies, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - University of California, Berkeley – Workshop on Environment and Politics, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 29-31)
  - University of California, Davis – African and African-American Studies Program, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - University of California, Davis – Pacific Bridges, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - University of California, Humanities Research Institute, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - University of California, Los Angeles – Interdisciplinary Workshop for Students of Developing Areas, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - University of California, Los Angeles – Southeast Asian Studies Program, 1996-2000 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - University of California, Los Angeles – Uongozi Institute, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago – Regional Worlds, 1995-1999 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
  - University of Colorado – Center for the American West, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - University of Georgia, 1995-1999 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - University of Ghana – International Centre for Music and Dance, 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - University of Kentucky, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - University of Massachusetts – Living Economy, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - University of Michigan – Center for Southeast Asian Studies, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - University of Minnesota – Breaking Boundaries, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - University of Pennsylvania – African Health Group, 1998-2000 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - University of Pennsylvania – Center for the Advanced Study of India, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - University of Pittsburgh, 1997-1999 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - University of Texas, El Paso – National Immigration Memorial, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - University of Washington – Southeast Asian Area Studies, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - University of Wisconsin – Philippine Environmental Photography, 1995-1998 (Box 9, Folder 21-22)
  - Vector Project, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Volkman grant lists, 1995-2001 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Volunteers in Asia, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Wellesley College – China Photo Project, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Williams, Carolyn – "What is Cultural Studies?", 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Woodrow Wilson Center, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - World History Association, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Worldwide Fund for Area Studies, 1997-1999 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Worldwide Workshop for Media, Arts and Culture Programmers, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Worldwide Workshop on Culture, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Worldwide Workshop on Education, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Yale University – Agrarian Studies, 1994-1997 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Yale University – Southeast Asian Studies, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Yayasan Asosiasi Tradisi Lisan, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 37)